Goodbye, oh world!
Goodbye.
God’s general CS UPTHEGROVE
1928 - 2018
For this purpose the Son of God was manifested, that He might destroy the works of the devil - 1 John 3:8
It is a good fight – a good warfare – the cause is good and the victory is sure,
if we continue, faithful and courageous.
The pastor of Miracle Valley Bible Training Centre and Miracle Valley International Revival Centre, the pastor of
healing, faith clinic is none other than Reverend C.S. Upthegrove from West Palm Beach, Florida.
Come on, let's give him a good hand.
This is the man whom God has sent.
Thank you, brother Allen.
Welcome to the Miracle Valley International Revival Centre.
I believe that God, today, is going to do a new thing.
God’s General C.S. Upthegrove
C.S. Upthegrove fought this good fight.
He fought it out and finished his course.
He did not give over till he was made more than a conqueror through God who loved him.
Evangelist C.S Upthegrove ranked among God's generals, ministered in the healing power of God
and preached the hope of the gospel of Jesus Christ to many in the US and around the world.
He began preaching the Word of God at the age of 15, and began seeing signs and wonders
in his revival meetings, where the sick were healed, the demon possessed were delivered
and the lost were saved.
In 1965, as a disciple of God's general A.A. Allen, he was ordained pastor of Miracle Valley in Arizona USA,
and people began coming from far and wide to receive their salvation, healing and deliverance.
This ministry continued until evangelist C.S. Upthegrove's peaceful passing.
In the late hours of Sunday, January 28th, 2018, the crown of life was placed upon his head.
Family and loved ones surrounded him, grateful to have had him in their midst.
Death to a good man is his release from the imprisonment of this world and his departure
to the enjoyments of another world.
He does not cease to be but is only removed from one world to another.
His legacy continues.
The best prayer we can offer our friends, family and loved ones is that the Lord Jesus Christ
may be with their spirits, to satisfy and save them and at the last, to receive them to Himself.
Many who believed as the God's generals did, are now before the throne, giving glory to the Lord.
May we be followers of them.
Goodbye, world!
From God’s General C.S. Upthegrove – 90 years
What a great comfort to a dying saint when he can look back upon his past life and say with Apostle Paul
in 2 Timothy 4:7, "I have fought the good fight, I have kept the faith, the doctrine of faith,
and the grace of faith.
Towards the end of our days, to be able to speak in this manner, what comfort -
unspeakable comfort - would it afford!
During the visit of God’s general C.S. Upthegrove to The SCOAN, he spent his quality time
with Prophet T.B. Joshua, prophesying about things to come and even his own death.
Now, let’s listen to God’s general C.S. Upthegrove prophesying concerning his passing unto glory.
Goodbye, oh world.
Goodbye.
God’s General C.S. Upthegrove
Well I told all my troubles goodbye
Goodbye to each tear and each sigh
This world where I roam cannot be my home
I'm bound for that land in the sky
Well I walk and I talk with my Lord
I feast everyday on His Word
Well Heaven is near and I can't stay here
So goodbye world goodbye
Goodbye, world!
Goodbye!
It takes faith to maintain your position to the end.
The beauty of our achievement is when we no longer live but that achievement is still there,
linger on in the eyes and ears of the children yet unborn. – T.B. Joshua
Goodbye, world!
Goodbye!
TT ROBERT BEGIER